<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>9 Digital Tech – Algorithms</title><link>https://tmcdigitech.github.io/9/assessment/algorithms/</link><description>Recent content in Algorithms on 9 Digital Tech</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://tmcdigitech.github.io/9/assessment/algorithms/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Assessment: 1: Algorithms Folio</title><link>https://tmcdigitech.github.io/9/assessment/algorithms/1-algorithms/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tmcdigitech.github.io/9/assessment/algorithms/1-algorithms/</guid><description>
&lt;h2 id="purpose">Purpose&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Practice and apply coding skills and computational thinking skills and knowledge in preparation for the individual programming project.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="task-description">Task Description&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Complete and submit each of the exercises in the Sequence, Selection, and Iteration sets.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Follow this link to &lt;a href="http://10.124.229.70:8080/">hand in your files&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="to-be-successful">To Be Successful&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Complete and demonstrate the above features with internal comments for all code.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="learning-behaviours">Learning Behaviours&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This task provides the following opportunities to develop and demonstrate the Learner Behaviours:&lt;/p>
&lt;dl>
&lt;dt>Driven&lt;/dt>
&lt;dd>Engages in all the aspects of the Design Process with initiative and seeks feedback during the development of their project.&lt;/dd>
&lt;dt>Curious&lt;/dt>
&lt;dd>Explores and tests ideas by asking questions, researching and through trial and error when learning new skills or developing solutions.&lt;/dd>
&lt;dt>Collaborative&lt;/dt>
&lt;dd>Works in teams to solve problems and create new information. Willingly shares new skills and knowledge and assists others and seeks assistance from peers.&lt;/dd>
&lt;dt>Connected&lt;/dt>
&lt;dd>Connects programming constructs and data structures to real life applications and is able to explore and discuss issues and ethical implications of their solution.&lt;/dd>
&lt;dt>Flexible Thinker&lt;/dt>
&lt;dd>Applies new knowledge and skills to solve problems and is able to adapt and recognize patterns in other solutions.&lt;/dd>
&lt;dt>Disciplined&lt;/dt>
&lt;dd>Motivated learner who demonstrates initiative by following a project management process to complete a project.&lt;/dd>
&lt;/dl></description></item></channel></rss>